Master of Business Economics, extensive Data analytics, SAP Application Support & Business Intelligence experience in Financial Services, Retail and Banking industries focusing on Accounting, Forecasting, Risk, CRM and Marketing. Apart from possessing very strong technical skills, Zita is a great team player to work with.

### **QAULIFICATION**

# Corp. Financial Analysis

- ♦ Hierarchical Master Data Management
- Financial modeling on budget, forecasting
- ♦ Revenue & Gross Margin, what-if analysis
- Reconciliation and variance analysis

# CRM, Marketing & Campaign

- Customer Transaction Analyses
- ♦ Customer RFM Model
- ♦ Campaign before and after analyses
- Market Share & Strategic Selection

#### Data Centric

- End-to-end data analysis with insights
- Data modeling, cleansing, transformation
- Data visualization, Dashboard
- Data Quality, MDM, Data flow chart

### Technical Skills

- Application Implementation: SAP, Process Flow
- Data: Advanced SQL, SQL Server, Access, Python
- Dashboard: Excel, Tableau, Power BI, Google Analytics
- ♦ Others: Jira, ServiceNow, Draw.io

### **EDUCATION**

- Master of Arts in Business Economics | GPA: A+| Wilfrid Laurier University | Sep 2020 Jun 2022
- Honors Bachelor of Arts in Economics | Wilfrid Laurier University | Sep 2016 May 2020
- Certificate | Google Analytics 2022 | SQL for Data Analysis Udcity 2022

# **WORK EXPERIENCE - INTERN**

### **Business Analyst | EDPYPF Services Inc.**

Mar 2022 - Aug 2022

- Collected business requirement; determined scope, KPI, workflow and layout to deliver the BRD
- Analyzed industry trends and customer data and validated the data integrity gaps using SQL & Python.
- Goal oriented Sales forecasting and planning; cost based budgeting for next year
- Designed CRM dashboards in **Tableau** with effective business KPI design to support targeted campaigns
- Enterprise-level reporting automation using Access & Excel for Monthly income statement report

### Analyst Consultant | Inossem Canada Inc.

May 2021 – Jan 2022

- Participated in SAP implementation for Segway Inc. and Powersports Canada as a Finance & Cost consultant;
- Gathered requirements; summarized pain points, and provided solutions with best-practices
- Cooperated with consultants from other modules such as SAP SD and MM on system integration testing
- identifying potential issues in business processes and discovering opportunities of system improvements
- Conducted Master Data Cleansing and standardization; configured enterprise level Product Hierarchy
- Managed multi-parties' communication and organized weekly meetings with customers to review CRs, incidents, and ad hock requests based on business logic & operational workflow

# Business Analyst | ZheShang Fund Management Co., Ltd

May 2019 - Sep 2019

- Maintained customer profile database to ensure client information accuracy and status up to date
- Analyzed campaign performance by region, product, and time through trending, variance analysis
- Prepared monthly investor performance report by products and investment categories
- Categorized customer groups on identifying potential targets; assessed churn risks through what-if analysis

# **Data Analyst | Oppein Home Group**

May 2017 - Sep 2017

- Coordinated with department of marketing, operations and finance to improve process efficiency
- Created and maintained 3-year sales forecasts and financial outlook reports
- Prepared sales and marketing KPI reports (average revenue per customer, sales funnel performance, impression, leads, and conversion rate)

### **ACADEMIC PROJECT**

- Bell Case Cash flow based Subscription Addition Strategy Selections | Apr 2021
- Market share Analysis Big Buy Marketing Strategy | Feb 2021